Woody Allen Papers, 1955-2012: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
Woody Allen Papers
1955-2012
TC002
Princeton University. Library. Dept. of Rare Books and Special Collections Manuscripts Division One Washington Road Princeton, New Jersey 08544 USA
26.8 linear feet 56 boxes
Allen, Woody, 1935-.
This collection contains writings by Woody Allen, acclaimed filmmaker and author. It includes copies of short stories, essays, articles, and the majority of Allen's films, along with original and various drafts of his prose work, plays and screenplays, some of which are either unpublished or unproduced.
Woody Allen is an American comedian, director, actor, and writer for television, theater, and film, as well as an author of several books and a musician. He was born Allen Stewart Konigsberg on December 1, 1935, in Brooklyn, New York. Early in his career, Allen was a stand-up comedian and comedy writer for television. He is perhaps best known for writing, directing and acting in many of his own films, and has won three Academy Awards: two in 1978 for Annie Hall for Best Director and Best Original Screenplay (co-written with Marshall Brickman) and Best Original Screenplay in 1987 for Hannah and Her Sisters. In addition, Allen also has received multiple awards and nominations for films such as Manhattan, The Purple Rose of Cairo, Crimes and Misdemeanors, and Match Point. In addition, he has contributed stories to magazines such as The New Yorker, written plays for Broadway including Don't Drink the Water and Play It Again, Sam, and performed around the world as a jazz clarinetist.
This collection contains copies of Allen's articles, essays, and short stories which appeared in The New Yorker, The New Republic, Kenyon Review, and Playboy, and elsewhere. There are also mimeographed screenplays by Allen for Bananas, Everything You Always Wanted to Know About Sex..., Don't Drink the Water, Play It Again, Sam, Stardust Memories, and The Front by Walter Bernstein, as well as the original drafts, revised with holograph corrections, for Take the Money and Run and Play It Again, Sam. In addition, there is printed material from newspapers and periodicals about Allen.
An addition to the papers includes original working drafts, typescripts with holograph corrections, rough drafts and notes for a number of Allen's prose writings, as well as original scripts for many of his popular screenplays, including Annie Hall, Hannah and her Sisters, Manhattan, The Purple Rose of Cairo, Radio Days, Sleeper, and Zelig. Also present is an original, unproduced script of "They Laughed at Fulton," written in 1955 when Allen was twenty.
A further addition consists of various typescript revisions, some with autograph corrections, of scripts for two motion pictures, Deconstructing Harry(1997) and Celebrity (1998) and scripts for two versions of a one-act play entitled "Central Park West" (1995). Also present is the original script (1998) for Sweet and Lowdown, a film released in 1999.
An addition in 2007 consists of fourteen archival boxes containing several autograph or original typed manuscripts for screenplays, books, and essays, including the movies Match Point (2005), Cassandra's Dream (2007), and Midnight in Barcelona, retitled Vicky Cristina Barcelona when it was released in 2008. Also included is one archival box of correspondence with publishers, copyright agreements and permissions for Allen's work, off-prints, and one archival box of printed material.
A later addition in late 2007 / early 2008 includes eight archival boxes of film and theater scripts along with two archival boxes containing an assortment of video cassette tapes and two long play vinyl records.
An addition to the papers in April 2008 consists of two archival boxes containing galley proofs of Allen's 2007 books, Mere Anarchy and The Insanity Defense, with a few autograph corrections by the author.
An addition to the papers in May 2012 consists of three archival boxes of drafts of screenplays for Midnight in Paris (2011), You Will Meet a Tall Dark Stranger (2010), Vicky Cristina Barcelona (2008) and To Rome with Love (2012). Also includes articles and short stories which appeared in The New Yorker and Zoetrope: All-Story from 2008-2012, and one stage play entitled Honeymoon Motel.
An addition in March 2014 includes drafts and fragments, including scripts for Blue Jasmine, Magic in the Moonlight, Irrational Man, and others.
An addition in September 2014 includes international press clippings and publicity materials regarding Allen's films and related events from 1995 to 2005. Included are a variety of printed and recorded interviews with Allen and several actors in his films, as well as some materials related to Allen's jazz band tours.
Organized into ten series by accession. There is no Box 51.
The photocopies contained in Boxes 3 and 4 are copies of the original manuscripts and typescripts contained in Boxes 1 and 2, respectively. Readers must use the photocopied materials from Boxes 3 and 4 for their research. They may not use the original drafts.
Gift of the author in 1980-2014 (TH1994-09, 1999-02, 2000-02, AM2007-112, 2008-49, 2008-98, 2012-93, 2014-80). Additional publicity materials were received via Lucy Darwin of Darwin Films in 2014 (2015-28).
The Manuscripts Division also holds the Jessica Lanier Collection of Woody Allen Set Photographs, which contains set photographs for Sweet and Lowdown, Small Time Crooks, and The Curse of the Jade Scorpion.
Humorists, American -- 20th century -- Manuscripts.; Motion picture plays.; Screenwriters -- United States -- Manuscripts.; Manuscripts.; Screenplays.; Theater/Film
- Series 1: First Series, 1982; 5.0 boxes
  Consists of manuscripts (both original and photocopies- please see access restrictions) of works by Woody Allen, including "Death: A Play," "A Brief Guide to Civil Disobedience," and "Fabrizio's (The Life of the Mind)," as well as others.
  The photocopies contained in Boxes 3 and 4 are copies of the original manuscripts and typescripts contained in Boxes 1 and 2, respectively. Readers must use the photocopied materials from Boxes 3 and 4 for their research. They may not use the original drafts. None of the manuscripts may be photocopied.
  Arranged alphabetically by title.
  - Bananas: Mimeographed filmscript (Combined Continuity), 1971 April 24; portion of 1 box (Folder 1)
  - "A Brief Guide to Civil Disobedience": 1 typescript, with corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 1)
  - "A Brief, Yet Helpful, Guide to Civil Disobedience": Xeroxed typescript, 1972 July 15; portion of 1 box (Folder 1)
  - "But Soft? Real Soft": Xeroxed typescript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 2)
  - "By Destiny Denied" ("Incident at Entwhistles"): Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 2)
  - "By Destiny Denied" ("Incident at Entwhistles"): Typescript, with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 2)
  - "By Destiny Denied" ("Incident at Entwhistles"): Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 2/23/76, 1976 February 23; portion of 1 box (Folder 3)
  - "The Condemned": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 3)
  - "The Condemned": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 11/22/77, 1977 November 21; portion of 1 box (Folder 4)
  - "Conversations With Helmholtz": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 4)
  - "Conversations With Helmholtz": Xeroxed typescript, 1970 October 2; portion of 1 box (Folder 5)
  - "Count Dracula", undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 6)
  - "Death: A Play": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 5)
  - "Death Knocks": Off-print, The New Yorker, 7/27/68, 1968 July 27; portion of 1 box (Folder 7)
  - "The Diet": 2 typescripts with revisions, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 6)
  - "The Diet": Xeroxed tearsheet, 1980 February 25; portion of 1 box (Folder 8)
  - "The Discovery and Use of the Fake Ink Blot in History (The Fake Ink Blot)": Xeroxed typescript, 1966 August; portion of 1 box (Folder 9)
  - Don't Drink the Water: Typescript, 1/7/70, 1970 January 7; portion of 1 box (Folder 2)
  - "Earl Monroe Interview for Sport Magazine", undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 7)
  - "The Early Essays: On Seeing a Tree in Summer": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 8)
  - "The Early Essays: On Seeing a Tree in Summer": Xeroxed tearsheet, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 10)
  - "The Emperor Ho Sin Had a Dream?": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 9)
  - Everything You Always Wanted to Know About Sex (What Makes a Man A Homosexual): Typescript with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 10)
  - Everything You Always Wanted to Know About Sex But Were Afraid to Ask: Mimeographed shooting script, 1972 August 26; portion of 1 box (Folder 3)
  - "Examining Psychic Phenomena": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 11)
  - "Examining Psychic Phenomena": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 10/7/72, 1972 October 7; portion of 1 box (Folder 11)
  - "Fabrizio's (The Life of the Mind)": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 12)
  - "Fabrizio's: Criticism an Response": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, undated, 1979 February 5; portion of 1 box (Folder 12)
  - "Fabulous Tales and Mythical Beasts": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 13)
  - "Fabulous Tales and Mythical Beasts": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 11/30/74, 1974 November 30; portion of 1 box (Folder 13)
  - "The Fake Ink Blot": Typescript with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 14)
  - "Feldman's Hostility": Typescript with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 15)
  - "Fine Times: An Oral Memoir": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 11/22/77, 1975 March 17; portion of 1 box (Folder 14)
  - "The First Humphrey Bogart Movie I Saw?": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 16)
  - The Front - By Walter Bernstein: Typescript, 8/13/75, 1975; portion of 1 box (Folder 4)
  - "A Giant Step for Mankind": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 17)
  - "A Giant Step for Mankind": Another version: Xeroxed typescript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 15)
  - "The Gossage-Vardebedian Papers:" Typescript with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 18)
  - "The Gossage-Vardebedian Papers": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 1/22/66, 1966 January 22; portion of 1 box (Folder 16)
  - "A Guide to Some of the Lesser Performed Ballets": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 19)
  - "A Guide to Some of the Lesser Performed Ballets": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 11/22/77, 1972 October 28; portion of 1 box (Folder 17)
  - "Hassidic Tales With a Guide to Their Interpretation By the Noted Scholar": Typescript with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 20)
  - "Hassidic Tales With a Guide to Their Interpretation By the Noted Scholar": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, undated, 1970 June 20; portion of 1 box (Folder 18)
  - "The Heavy": Original draft, typescript with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 21)
  - "A House is Definitely Not a Home": Original draft, typescript with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 22)
  - "How I Became a Comedian": Xeroxed tearsheet, Chicago Daily News, 8/3/?, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 19)
  - "If the Impressionists Were Dentists": Xeroxed typescript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 20)
  - "I Have, So That Posterity May Record?": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 23)
  - "The Irish Genius": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 24)
  - "The Irish Genius": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Republic, 2/22/75, 1975 February 22; portion of 1 box (Folder 21)
  - "The Kugelmass Episode": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 25)
  - "The Kugelmass Episode": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 5/2/77, 1977 May 2; portion of 1 box (Folder 22)
  - "A Little Louder, Please:" Typescript with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 26)
  - "A Little Louder, Please": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 5/28/66, 1966 May 28; portion of 1 box (Folder 23)
  - "A Look at Organized Crime": Original tearsheet, The New Yorker, 8/15/70, 1970 August 15; portion of 1 box (Folder 24)
  - "Lovborg's Women Considered": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 10/28/74, 1974 October 28; portion of 1 box (Folder 25)
  - "The Lunatic's Tale": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 27)
  - "The Lunatic's Tale": Revised draft, xeroxed typescript with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 28)
  - "The Lunatic's Tale": Xeroxed typescript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 26)
  - "Match Wits With Inspector Ford": Original draft, typescript with manuscript corrections, 1972 December; portion of 1 box (Folder 1)
  - "Match Wits With Inspector Ford": Xeroxed tearsheet, Playboy, December 1972, 1972 December; portion of 1 box (Folder 27)
  - "The Metterling List (Ah Metterling, He's Dead)": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 2)
  - "The Metterling List (Ah Metterling, He's Dead)": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 5/10/69, 1969 May 10; portion of 1 box (Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous Manuscripts: Page number 6 and beginning: "What then, is beautiful?", undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Manuscripts: Notes on European Hotel Stationary, Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 4)
  - "Mr. Big": Xeroxed typescript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 29)
  - "My Apology": Original draft, typescript with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 5)
  - "My Apology": Xeroxed typescript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 30)
  - "My Philosophy": Original draft typescript, manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 6)
  - "My Philosophy": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 12/27/69, 1969 December 27; portion of 1 box (Folder 31)
  - "My Speech to the Graduating Class:" Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 7)
  - "My Speech to the Graduating Class": Revised draft typescript with manuscript corrections, Xeroxed typescript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 32)
  - "Nefarious Times We Live In": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 8)
  - "Nefarious Times We Live In": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Republic, 11/22/75, 1975 November 22; portion of 1 box (Folder 33)
  - "No Kaddish of Weinstein": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 3/3/75, 1975 March 3; portion of 1 box (Folder 34)
  - "Notes on the Comedian: Mort Sahl": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 9)
  - "Notes From the Overfed": Typescript with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 10)
  - "Notes From the Overfed": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 3/16/68, 1968 March 16; portion of 1 box (Folder 35)
  - "On Being Struck By Lightning": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 11)
  - "On Death": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 12)
  - "Philosophy is to Science as?": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 13)
  - Play it Again, Sam (Screenplay): Original draft, typescript with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 14)
  - Play it Again, Sam (Screenplay): Mimeographed film script, 1971 September 2; portion of 1 box (Folder 5)
  - "The Pussycat Papers": Original draft manuscript with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 15)
  - "The Query": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 16)
  - "The Query": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Republic, 9/18/76, 1976 September 18; portion of 1 box (Folder 36)
  - "Remembering Needleman": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 17)
  - "Remembering Needleman": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Republic, 7/24/76, 1976 July 24; portion of 1 box (Folder 37)
  - "Reminiscences: Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 18)
  - "Reminiscences": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 12/29/75, 1975 December 29; portion of 1 box (Folder 38)
  - "Retribution": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 19)
  - "Retribution": Xeroxed tearsheet, The Kenyon Review, Summer 1980, portion of 1 box (Folder 39)
  - "The Schmeed Memoirs": Xeroxed typescript, clean copy, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 40)
  - "The Scrolls": Original draft typescript with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 20)
  - "The Scrolls": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Republic, 8/31/74, 1974 August 31; portion of 1 box (Folder 41)
  - "Selections From the Allen Notebooks": Revised draft typescript with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 21)
  - "Selections From the Allen Notebooks": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, undated, 1973 November 5; portion of 1 box (Folder 42)
  - "The Shallowest Man": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 22)
  - "The Shallowest Man:" Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 11/27/75, 1980; portion of 1 box (Folder 43)
  - "Spring Bulletin": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 4/29/67, 1967 April 29; portion of 1 box (Folder 44)
  - Stardust Memoirs: Filmscript, 9/24/80, 1980 September 24; portion of 1 box (Folder 6)
  - "Slang Origins": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 23)
  - "Sure I Stole, Fellas?": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 24)
  - Take the Money and Run: Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 25)
  - Television Special: Original draft typescript with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 26)
  - "The Truth at Last": Original draft typescript with manuscript corrections, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 27)
  - "The UFO Menace": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 28)
  - "The UFO Menace" Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 6/13/77, 1977 June 13; portion of 1 box (Folder 45)
  - "Viva Vargas!": Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 29)
  - "Viva Vargas!": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, no title, undated, portion of 1 box (Folder 46)
  - "The Whore of Mensa": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, undated, 1974 December 16; portion of 1 box (Folder 47)
  - "Yes, But Can the Steam Engine Do This?": Xeroxed tearsheet, The New Yorker, 10/8/66, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 48)
  - "Youth and Age:" Original draft manuscript, undated; portion of 1 box (Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous Articles about Woody Allen, 1972-1980; portion of 1 box (Folder 7)
- Series 2: Additions, 1994; 5.0 boxes
  Note: The following manuscripts are listed on the donor's original list of Contents for the 1994 gift (TH1994-09); however, they have not been located and/or identified: "Letter to My Father" (abortive attempts & drafts) "Match Wits with Inspector Ford" (original draft) several unpublished fragments
  Arranged by genre of material.
  - Prose Writings, undated; 17.0 folders
    - "Confessions of a Burglar": original TMs (with autograph revisions), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - "Consider Kaplan...": original TMs & AMs, unpublished story, undated; 3.0 versions (Folder 2)
    - "Death of Socrates": original AMs (draft), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - "The Diet, Guilt, American Style": original AMs (draft), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - "Feldman's Hostility": original AMs (draft), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - "Fine Times": original AMs (draft), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - "Guide to Civil Disobedience": original AMss (various drafts), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - "If the Impressionists Had Been Dentists": original AMs & TMs (drafts), undated; 2.0 versions (Folder 8)
    - "Letter to My Father": original AMs (draft), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - "Luig's Villa Nova Restaurant"; "Pasta, as an expression of Italian Neo-Realistic starch....": original TMs (draft), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - "Lovborg's Women": original AMs (draft), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - "No Kaddish for Weinstein": original AMs & TMs (drafts), undated; 2.0 versions (Folder 12)
    - "Remembering Needleman": original TMs (draft), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
    - "The Schmeed Memoirs": original TMs (draft), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
    - "Slang Origins" (Argotnaut): original AMs (draft), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
    - "Whore of Mensa": original AMs & TMs (drafts), undated; 2.0 versions (Folder 16)
    - Unidentified writings: misc. AMss notes & drafts, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
  - Scripts, 1955-1990; 5.0 boxes (1 partial)
    - Alice, 1990; 2.0 folders
      - original script, early draft, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
      - line script (copy), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
    - Annie Hall: script (copy), early draft, 1977; 1.0 folder (Folder 20)
    - Another Woman, 1988; 2.0 folders
      - original script, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
      - revised script, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 22)
    - Bananas t ("El Weirdo"): script (copy), last 12 pages missing, 1971; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Broadway Danny Rose: original script, 1984; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Crimes and Misdemeanors ("Brothers"), 1989; 2.0 folders
      - script (copy), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
      - lined script (copy), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - "Death": one-act play, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
      see: Sex and Death, 1975
    - [Everything you Always Wanted to Know About Sex But Were Afraid to Ask]: original AMs (draft) of Gene Wilder's sketch, 1972; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - The Floating Light Bulb (A Second Hand Memory): original script, with revisions, 1981; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - "God": original AMs (draft), one-act play, 1975; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Hannah and Her Sisters, circa 1986; 3.0 folders (Folder 1)
      - undated notes; original script, early draft, pp. 1-90, 1.0 item
      - original script, early draft, pp. 1-118, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
      - original script, pp. 1-119, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Husbands and Wives: original script, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - The Jazz Baby: original script, unshot filmscript (retitled Sweet and Lowdown), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Love and Death, circa 1975; 2.0 folder (Folder 2)
      - original script, undated; 1.0 item
      - misc. pages, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - Manhattan: original script, 1979; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - The Purple Rose of Cairo, circa 1985; 2.0 folder (Folder 5)
      - outline & notes, undated; 1.0 item
      - original script, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
    - "The Query": original script, draft, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
    - Radio Days, circa 1987; 2.0 folder (Folder 8)
      - original script, undated; 1.0 item
      - misc. pages, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
    - "Sex " and "Death": original scripts, 2 one-act plays, 1975; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
    - Shadows and Fog: original script, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
    - Sleeper, circa 1973; 2.0 folder (Folder 1)
      - original script, "Life in the Future", undated; 1.0 item
      - original script, early draft, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
    - Stardust Memories: original script, 1980; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
    - "They Laughed at Fulton": original script, unproduced, 1955; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
    - Zelig: original script, 1983; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
    - Unidentified Script: original untitled & unshot TMs (characters include Rifkin, Carlotta, Moses, Kate), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
- Series 3: Additions, 1999; 5.0 boxes
  Consists of scripts for Celebrity, Central Park West, and Deconstructing Harry.
  - Scripts, 1995-1998; 5.0 boxes